<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Plasteel Surgery (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.PlasteelSurgery</packageId>
  <author>Mlie</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/PlasteelSurgery</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies />
  <loadAfter />
  <description>
    Update of Neon1028s mod
    https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1569056149

[img]https://raw.githubusercontent.com/emipa606/RimWorld-Wrapper/master/Notice.png[/img]

    Support-chat:
    https://discord.gg/SuhwVpM

    Non-steam version:
    https://github.com/emipa606/PlasteelSurgery

    --- Original Description ---
	In a world with space travel, cryo freezing, and hats why should anyone have to be ugly? New research into the medical application of plasteel has resulted in advanced surgical techniques to allow doctors to alter a colonist's body type, sex, or even beauty. All research has the prerequisite of Hospital Bed. Each surgery will require some plasteel, industrial medicine or better, and a good surgeon who's got a little bit of an artistic side.

    Includes:

    Body Modification: Unlocks surgeries to change a pawn's body type to Fat, Thin, Hulking, Masculine, or Feminine. (Change will not be visable until they wake up from the anesthetic)

    Sex Reassignment: Change a pawn's biological sex. (This does not change their body type)

    Facial Reconstruction: Increase or decrease the beauty of a pawn by one level. To take a pawn from ugly to beautiful will require multiple surgeries. If any surgery happens to fail the beauty of the patient will instead be dropped by one level, so make sure you have a good doctor. This research comes in three tiers.

    Basic:
    Staggeringly Ugly ? Ugly ? Plain ? Pretty ? Beautiful
    Intermediate:
    Staggeringly Ugly ? Ugly ? Plain ? Pretty ? Beautiful
    Advanced:
    Staggeringly Ugly ? Ugly ? Plain ? Pretty ? Beautiful

    Compatibility: This mod can be added or removed from existing saves with out problem. It should be compatible with all mods and has been tested against several. If you happen to find a mod it doesn't work with please leave a post on this mod's Steam Workshop Discussion page.

    Known Problems: Changing the sex of a pawn who is in a relationship can have some side effects. If the new sex is not the preferred sex of the partner (ie. taking a hetero man-woman couple and changing the woman to a man) they will not automatically break up and will still share a bed, but it looks like they stop "getting some lovin'".
  </description>
</ModMetaData>